Thank you for watching!
My name is Koei Takano.
Well, I'm often called Koei as it is.
My grandma calls me Kouchan.
It's June 20th.
Okinawa Prefecture.
I'm large.
I am right-handed.
I have an older sister.
I have a dog at home.
He is a turf dog.
Chum Point is
Here.
I don't know if it's an egg bow.
I don't know if it's an eggbow, but it's here.
He's got his eye on the drop stone.
My pace
What is it?
I'm an INFP.
My hobbies are baking.
I play basketball, sports, and many other things.
I can say Picasso's real name.
I can.
Pablo Diego Jose Francisco de Paula Juan de Pomuseno
maria de los remedios crispin crispiano
Della Santi Cimatrena do Luis y Picasso
Is.
Just hanging out at home.
Eno.
I watch movies and YouTube all the time.
Green and blue.
It's winter.
I like AAA.
I like Mr. Kennara.
I like TV shows like “I Am Adventure Boy” a lot.
Favorite movie
Let's see, there is a Hollywood movie called Hachi.
It's very moving. Please watch it! It's insanely moving, you guys should see it.
Favorite radio.
Well, I've been listening to a radio show called “School of Rock” since I was in elementary and middle school.
I listened to it my whole life in elementary and middle school.
I loved it so much!
Favorite YouTube
I don't really watch YouTubers, but...
But, what an amazing YouTuber!
Um, Orochinju...
He's pretty funny.
Favorite TikTokker?
TikTokker... Wow, that's a tough one.
But I like Maury Shute...
I learn a lot by watching them.
I use them as a reference.
I'm Chika.
I'm Chika...
She can't speak, but she tries her best.
She can't speak well, but she tries to convey her feelings.
And she's so kind.
Kindness that doesn't ask for anything in return.
It's very touching.
Well, it's difficult to say who is my favorite character in Chikawa.
It's difficult to say.
But I'll tell you why.
Chi-kawa is an amazing character.
Of course, Chikawa is the main character.
I mean, of course, she is the main character, but
but all the other characters
but all the other characters have their own unique personalities
They're all so cute!
I mean, I already knew about the existence of Chi-kawa
I knew he existed.
I'm the only one...
It's a strange way to enter the show.
There is a song sung by Yae Ari.
It's called “Hitorigotsu”.
A song... A song.
I first heard of “The Cute Little Girl” from the song.
My favorite anime
Toriko.
Melon.
Tomato and Nanto.
Calpis water.
Favorite candy
Pureed gummy bears.
Melons.
Dogs.
Sometimes
A forest
My favorite emoji
This smiley face.
Not the one with the face.
I like the one with two lines.
I also like basketball and swimming.
I also like watching baseball.
Favorite number?
I like the number 5.
I like the shape of it.
I like to cook eggs.
Subjects I am good at
Well, I used to be good at geography and memorizing things.
I used to be good at it, but now I've forgotten everything.
Mathematics.
Well, my grandfather was an architect.
So I dreamed of becoming an architect.
The karaoke box is
Shota Shimizu's
Melody to the fragrance of flower soul by Shota Shimizu, right?
I listen to a song called “Contact Case” by Saucy Dock.
It's a nice song!
Ms. Reina!
It's a song called “Uttatane” by Ms. Reina.
It's a love song.
It's a love song, but it's pretty pop for a love song. It's kind of pop for a love song.
It's not so much that I want people to listen to the lyrics, but more that I want them to listen to the sound behind the song and her voice without thinking about anything else.
I want you to listen to the sound behind this song and her voice without thinking about anything.
Ayume Imazu's song “Tangerine”... that song... that song...
The sound in the back is really nice, and his sense of rhythm, I don't know if it's called “5th incarnation” or what...
I don't know if it's called the 5th reincarnation, but it's this feathery feeling like I must have been exposed to music when I was a little kid, and I can get into a super groove to it.
I like the song “My Melancholy and My Moody Girlfriend”.
The arrangement of the live version at Tokyo Dome was so genius!
The arrangement of the live version at the Tokyo Dome was so genius that it really shocked me, and I've loved it ever since.
I bought Kana Nishino's album with my mom.
There are many people I admire
Of course I love singing, and I was really influenced by Chota Shimizu's singing style.
I also want to be a member of a group like AAA.
I admire people who can sing and dance well.
I also admire Daichi Miura a lot.
The lock screen of my phone right now is
What's this?
It's some kind of scenery.
What do you collect now?
Chikawa goods.
I collect them when I go out of town.
When I go to the arcade...
I take some of them.
I buy stickers when I find them in town.
My treasures are
A wallet that my grandma bought me as a graduation present from junior high school.
What do you want most now?
I guess so.
Well...
Love from everyone in LaBarto.
What about musical instruments?
I took piano lessons for about two months.
But I can't play it.
So the instrument I'd like to be able to play is piano.
But I'd also love to play the guitar.
I'm an indoor musician.
There is a World Heritage Site called Shirakami Sanchi.
There's a huge forest there.There is a huge forest there.
I feel like I can feel the power.
I've wanted to go there since I was a little girl.
The Shirakami Sanchi.
Yes, sir.
I like to look at the scenery, so I like to walk along the river, or take the train to a station I never go to.
When I'm depressed, even if I'm told not to be depressed anymore, I'm still depressed.
I just accept it and wait for time to solve the problem.
Well... Well...
I usually do this straight forward way.
I think it's important to use a primer.
I think it's important to have a good primer.
I love it!
Of course, I get really excited when I meet you all for the first time in a long time or when I see you on a big stage, but I get really excited when I see you all on a big stage.
But for me, it's the signals.
I get really excited when the traffic lights are all green when I'm moving.
I go to bed very early, but I also wake up very early.
I wake up at 6 a.m. or 4 a.m. at the earliest, which is about 8 hours.
I don't know if I can call it a routine these days, but...
of
I drink Yuzu tea.
I think my previous life was...
Maybe I was a caterpillar or something.
If I were to be reincarnated, I would be me again.
I like sweets.
Rice.
Kelp
Hanpen and ajitama (seasoned eggs).
Tuna, of course.
Who would you like to meet?
Bruno Mars.
In the past.
Getting this audition?
Yes. School.
Adult.
Older sister.
Youngest child
Natural water Natural Water
innocent and innocent
Omoro classmate
Cute little brother
Muscle Man
I've lost a lot of weight lately, though... spring
I am...
I like him a lot, except for his blue heart.
I like it a lot. But my favorite is
Uh, Gibb It Try.
Favorite costume?
Oh, I like the Glory Days outfit a lot.
Something you'd like to do?
Well, I'd like to do field day.
Gymnastics.
But I'd also like to do relays and obstacle relays.
I'd like to do that.
Or maybe AAA's “I love you, but I can't love you.
I love you but I can't love you.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's where I'm going.
Oh, I don't know.
I wonder what's popular now.
Oh, but...
I don't know, anime...
I mean, I've been watching a lot of anime.
I mean, I'll tell you what's popular, I'll tell you what's popular, I'll tell you what's popular.
Good night.
Hmm!
Haruma?
I've been...
I've been into watching live video games.
They're really funny.
Basically.
He was fighting a really strong boss and beat him.
He fought a really strong boss and beat him.
There were three of them, and two of them were really strong. There were three of them, and two of them were really strong.
I beat two of them, and they're really strong.
But if you don't defeat the other one, he'll come back forever.
The moment when I realized that fact was really interesting.
That's right.
Hmm...
Hmmm...
I'd love to become Haruma and enjoy campus life.
I'd like to enjoy campus life as Haruma.
Before the concert...
I have a routine.
I have a routine of shutting up.
You know...
I vocalize a lot until about an hour or so.
After that, I suddenly stop talking.
I haven't told anyone.
This is the kind of information
I like it lately.
People think I don't cook.
I sometimes say on social media that I cook.
Lately I've been doing it quite a bit.
I made fried chicken.
Well, my goal as Love One is to go to a bigger stage with Love Art.
I want to go to a bigger stage with all the Love Art members.
But my goal is to go to a bigger stage with Love Art.
Yes...yes...
Of course, by the time we get there
I'm sure I'll have to go to a big live house or a hall or something like that.
I'm sure you've already experienced it.
But my goal is to perform in an arena.
Well, guys...
I'm always like this.
I don't know...
Right?
People say I don't know what I'm thinking.
But I love you guys so much.
I love the Love Out team so much.
Hey, guys... Hey, guys.
Keep up the good work!
Next time preview